Sure, we'll join
It's just two drinks
It's on me, drink as much as you want
Why do you care so much about your fiancée?
The reporters are over there
We're just business partners
Cut the tricks
Siqi, this one's for you
Thanks for making our love possible
She can't drink anymore
She can't hold her liquor
I'll take it
This invisible war
is really something
Jiang Lai really has some tricks up her sleeve
She clearly seduced Young Master Sheng first
yet she made Lin Siqi
look like the one who cheated first
Why do you care so much?
Make sure to write a good article
Stick to one core message
Jiang Lai is the sweet angel
comforting the heartbroken rich heir
How about I title it like this?
Lin Siqi Cheats with Poor Country Boy
Sheng Yuanzhou Struggles to Heal from Heartbreak
Young Master Sheng
Who told you to write that?
Miss Jiang
Delete it and rewrite it
Lin Siqi's name can't appear at all
Did you hear me?
Yes
That Sheng heir is such a simp
He's already been cuckolded
and he's still protecting Lin Siqi
Jiang Lai
What are you doing?
Let me tell you
whatever is between us
leave Siqi out of it
Feeling upset?
If Siqi gets hurt at all
you'll never step foot in the Sheng house again
Then you don't want the Key of Fate?
You won't be Sheng Yuanzhou anymore?
Let me tell you
I won't take the blame of being The other woman
After all, in your engagement
the one who betrayed you was Lin Siqi
I just want what's fair
What?
Our business
isn't finished yet
Well?
It's just acting
Why so dedicated?
What do you think?
Didn't you have the paparazzi delete
all of Lin Siqi's photos?
Aren't you playing the heartless jerk?
Then I'll play along
Fine
Here comes the main event
Shoot it, shoot it!
Shoot, shoot!
Why'd he close the curtains?
Must be premium content
What's going on?
Closing the curtains this early?
How are reporters supposed to get shots?
We've got enough photos already
No need to shoot more
I don't mind making it real
Jiang Lai, you know better than anyone
I'm Zhang Xiaobei
I know
The Sheng family's money, and you
I want it all
Sorry
I don't care
Are you saving yourself for Lin Siqi?
What's it to you?
Even if you're hopelessly devoted
in Lin Siqi's eyes
you'll always be Sheng Yuanzhou
And Sheng Yuanzhou
will always be her beloved Zhang Xiaobei
Sure, you can save yourself for her
but she might not stay faithful to you
What the hell do you mean?
I mean
I didn't just invite the two of them
to dinner by the beach
What else did you do?
Worried?
They're the real couple now
Anything they do is perfectly reasonable, isn't it?
Speak
My patience has limits
Tell me
Room 410
I booked them a honeymoon suite
The number you dialed is powered off
We...
They must've made a mistake
I'll call the front desk right now
Help me
You can't fight those in power
You need some backbone
How am I supposed to have backbone?
What's done is done
Your dad won't be able to oppose it then
No, don't
Don't you come any closer
I won, you promised
No, no, no!
Open up!
Open up! Open up!
Sheng Yuanzhou
What are you doing here?
You animal!
Sheng Yuanzhou, what are you doing?
I...
Let go of me!
Are you out of your mind?
Barging in here just to start trouble
What, you two playing chess?
Don't play dumb with me
Just spit it out
It's nothing, I just...
If it's nothing, then leave
Actually, I
wanted to invite you both for a drink
No
Come on, it's rare for us to be here
Come on, let's go
Hurry up and get out, you hear me?
Let's go
Why are you pushing me?
I heard New Pants is playing today
having a small live show
New Pants
Sure
How is it?
Nice atmosphere, right?
Where's the band you mentioned?
Maybe I misheard.
You lied to us, didn't you?
I didn't lie to you.
All right, don't be mad.
Worst case, dinner's on me.
Come on, sit, sit.
You too, sit down. Come on.
Give me a second.
I honestly think this place
has a pretty great vibe.
So I wanted to invite you to check it out.
So, not bad, right?
This next song,
I'd like to dedicate to my girlfriend,
Lin Siqi.
Thank you for always staying by my side,
and for treasuring
someone who isn't all that great.
Siqi.
Do you like him?
Who?
The guy singing up there.
Of course.
Then...
Do you like him, or Zhang Xiaobei?
Isn't he Zhang Xiaobei?
I mean...
If he weren't Zhang Xiaobei,
would you still like him?
Not Zhang Xiaobei?
Why does Sheng Yuanzhou care so much about me?
I'll peel the shrimp for you.
No.
Just wait.
I mean...
Siqi can't eat seafood.
What if...
I mean, just what if.
This guy...
He's like the Zhang Xiaobei you remember,
but he also doesn't quite seem like
the Zhang Xiaobei from your memories.
You...
Would you be able to tell the difference?
I would.
You're that confident?
I...
I definitely...
could spot him
in a crowd for sure.
I...
No...
I didn't see anything.
Sorry to interrupt.
You misunderstood, Siqi.
Siqi!
Don't come any closer.
What happened yesterday was a misunderstanding.
Don't take it to heart.
Can't you just stay away from me?
Even if you asked, I wouldn't come close.
Good.
From now on, we go our separate ways.
Let's go, let's go.
And one more thing.
About us sleeping in the same bed yesterday...
Don't tell anyone.
You too.
Sheng Yuanzhou.
After we get back this time,
I'll make it clear to my dad that I'm calling off the engagement.
Since I was little,
I grew up with Jiang Lai.
It's the first time I've seen her care so much about someone.
She...
She just has a tough exterior, soft heart.
She always speaks with sarcasm and provocation,
but it's really to hide her true feelings.
She's afraid of getting hurt.
So from now on, you need to be more patient with her.
Also...
About you getting a room with Zhu Yutong,
I won't say a word.
But I hope you won't do that again.
All right.
Let's go.
Bye.
Bye. Have a safe trip.
Siqi, wait for me.
I'll be back by your side soon.
Xiaobei.
I already called a car for myself.
You can go back first.
I'll take a cab and see you home.
No need.
A lot's happened lately.
I want some time alone to think.